

AMIRUL HAMZA ABDULLAH

Phone: +60 16340 9344 | Email: amirul.hamza92@gmail.com | Address: Cheras, Wilayah Persekutuan Kuala Lumpur 56000

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Ambitious student who has completed coursework in human resources economic and master degree in Econometrics. Possesses strong interpersonal skills and a desire for a career in research and management. Economic student equipped with strong interpersonal skills as well as extensive knowledge of statistic and research methodology. Built up with experience on research with excellent communication skills and strong motivation to succeed.

EXPERIENCE

EXECUTIVE BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT

Career Centre Malaysia

Selangor, Malaysia February 2017-September 2017

- Organized training health and safety training at Career Centre Malaysia.
- Organized Career And Education Fair.
- Prepared proposal for Project at Human Resources Development Fund (HRDF) and Skill Development Fund Corporation (PTPK).
- Organized the project workshops for B40 community funded by PTPK.
- Data Entry about 400 respondents and analyze the data using Excel (Descriptive analysis).
- Prepared invitation letter and doing admin stuff (Ad hoc).

RESEARCH ASSISTANCE, UKM

Level of Education and Wage

Selangor, Malaysia February 2016 – December 2016

- Published one article about analysis of "Educational Qualification Requirement In Malaysia's Services Sector -Under Or Over Education Issue".
- Presenting the research finding at The Malaysian National Economic Conference (PERKEM).
- Analyze data using two stage least square (2TLS) with instrument variable using SPSS 22.
- Organized data using SPSS 22.
- Research and summarize literature review.

EDUCATION =

UNIVERSITI KEBANGSAAN MALAYSIA (3.53)

Master Degree Economic Majoring Econometrics

Selangor, Malaysia September 2015 – February 2017

UNIVERSITI MALAYSIA SABAH (3.19)

Bachelor Degree Economic Majoring Human Resources (Hons)

Sabah, Malaysia September 2012 – August 2015

SMK BANDAR TUN HUSSEIN ONN 2 (3.19) Selangor, Malaysia

Sijil Tinggi Peperiksaan Malaysia

January 2010 – December 2011

SMK BANDAR DAMAI PERDANA

Siji Peperiksaan Malaysia

Selangor, Malaysia January 2005 – December 2009

ACHIEVEMENT

2016	Presenter in The Malaysian National Economic Conference 2016
2014	Presenter in the 1 st Regional Conference on Campus Sustainability, UMS
2013-2014	Secretariat Kediaman Cemerlang Dinamik (Exco Welfares and Moral)
2013	Organized in welcoming new Student at Kolej Kediaman Cemerlang Dinamik as a committee member
2013	Organized in week of Insprasi Sanubari as a Team leader on site preparation
2012 - 2013	Secretariat Kediaman Cemerlang Dinamik (exco welfares and Security)
2012	Organize in Photoshop course as a vice director

COMPENTENCE		
LANGUAGE		
Malay	$\Diamond\Diamond\Diamond\Diamond\Diamond$	
English	$\diamond \diamond \diamond \diamond \diamond$	
PERSONAL SKILLS		
Communication	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Flexibility	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Team Player	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Independent	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Creativity	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Problem Solve	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Analytical-Thinking	\diamond \diamond \diamond \diamond	
TECHNICAL SKILLS		
Microsoft Office	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
SPSS 22	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Eviews 9.0	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
Stata 13	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
R software	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$	
REFERENCE =		

Mr. Faizal Radzi.

Managing DirectorElite Career Centre Sdn Bhd

Tel: 014 339 8182

Email: faizal@careercentre.com.my

YM Tengku Zuhri Tengku Abdul Aziz Chairman

Silver Wolves Advisory Group Malaysia (SWAG) Tel: 012-6531977

Email: zuhri@swagmalaysia.com

Prof Dr Ishak Yussof (SV) Professor

Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia

Tel: 03 8921 5767 Email: iby@ukm.my